Why is Finland in NATO a friend,
Почему если Финляндия в НАТО - это друг
but Ukraine in NATO then not a
а Украина в НАТО тогда не
friend?
друг
Why was Ukraine probably more like this,
Почему наверное Украина более такая была
you know, provocative or
знаете вызывающая что ли
something? Uh-huh Hello
Угу Здравствуйте
Hello, such a
Здравствуйте прикид такой
cool outfit I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
классный Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
Where are you from prostrate I'm from SN Oh lki It's
откуда ниц я откуда СН Ох лки У вас
probably light out now for you  polar
наверно светло сейчас да ти полярная
night it’s already
ночь
bright there are already people from Murmansk the
светло попадались уже люди с Мурманска
sun is really shining at night and the World Cup you’re communicating,
ВС а ЧМ общаетесь
for example, it’s just
например просто
interesting What do you want
Интересно так А о чём хотите
to talk about Well, ask questions if
пообщаться Ну задавайте вопросы так если
not about the war I would like about the war but you have
не о войне Я бы хотел о войне но у вас
other topics about what No, I’m something
другие темы о чём Да нет я что-то
I want when You understand, when you talk about the war
хочу когда Понимаете когда о войне
it starts, this
говоришь начинается вот это друг друга
starts with swearing at each other, this
матюками начинает этот
one is sophisticated without swearing
то утончённый без матюков
Well, let’s try, you’ll like it, yes But
ну Давайте попробуем вам понравится да А
let’s whose Crimea Yes, I’m a blogger now I’m
вот Давайте чей Крым Да я блогер сейчас
streaming How many subscribers are there
Стрим веду Сколько подписчиков
200-odd thousand subscribers on the stream
подписчиков 200 с чем-то тысяч на стриме
Hello everyone All Ukrainians are uh different from different
привет Все украинцы ээ разные с разного
from different countries of the world do you want uh we have such a
с разных стран мира хочешь ээ есть такая
promotion for example people write questions in the chat
у нас акция например люди пишут в чат
I will voice them and you answer But this
вопросы Я озвучу и ты отвечаешь Но это о
will be about politics Come on Pou So let's
политике будет Давай Поу Так давайте
My name is Andrey your name is like Ivan Ivan so
Меня Андрей зовут тебя как Иван Иван так
People are doing a blitz  for Ivan, that is, a
Народ делаем блиц для Ивана то есть
short question and also short answers,
короткий вопрос и также ответы короткие
not too much of a long rant there,
не сильно там долго разглагольствовать
that they just answered the following So
что просто там ответили следующий Так
let's ask questions for Ivan from
давайте вопросы для Ивана из
Murmansk right person from Poland
Мурманска спра человек из Польши
asks Poles friends of
спрашивает поляки друзья
Russia Poles friends so friends
России поляки друзья так друзья
further now there they just have a delay of
дальше сейчас там просто у них задержка
30 seconds and  they Therefore, if I
секунд 30 идёт а они Поэтому если я
said they heard and as long as they write
сказал они услышали и пока они напишут
so now they will go. So the questions are:
так сейчас пойдут Так вопросы
How many Russians should Die for
вот Сколько россиян должно Умереть чтобы
him he for you to start
он он чтоб ты начал их
counting them Yes, it’s a difficult question I can’t
считать Да слож вопрос не могу
understand Anna asks how much
понял Анна спрашивает сколько
he writes in English I’ll translate How much is
по-английски пишет я переведу Сколько
your life worth like you
стоит твоя жизнь как ты
you think priceless priceless so Alex
считаешь бесценно бесценно так Алекс
asks whose
спрашивает чей
Crimea is
Крым
Russian I got it Artyom asks Murmansk
русский Понял Артём спрашивает Мурманск
is the world yes I got it Igor asks Do
- это мира да Понял Игорь спрашивает
you like it when Russians kill
Тебе нравится когда русские убивают
other peoples
другие народы
I think I misunderstood No
сви Мне кажется это неправильно понял No
about asking you support Putin
про спрашивает ты Путина поддерживаешь
Yes I understand My president Galina Asks
Да понял Мой президент Галина Спрашивает
Do you know that purple  - this is the color of
ли знаешь Ты что фиолетовый - это цвет
schizophrenia, I didn’t know, for example,
шизофреники я не знал например
purple - this is pink, I understand I don’t know,
фиолетовый - это розовый понял Не знаю
but I’m not a Renik
но я не реник
Uh-huh Dima asks his wife or
Угу Дима спрашивает жена или
Crimea, his wife so
Крым жена так
Ponya Rostislav asks there is a car Yes
Поня Ростислав спрашивает есть машина Да
Two Oleg asks Finland is a friend if
Две Олег спрашивает Финляндия друг если
he joined
вступила в
NATO Finland is a
НАТО Финляндия
friend so Lady asks Hamas is also a
друг так Леди спрашивает Хамас тоже
friend  Russia's friends Russia I didn't
друзь России друзья России м не
bother, I don't know Well, I mean, I understand
заморачивался не знаю Ну в смысле понял
And she asks, will you go to war if they take
А она спрашивает пойдёшь на войну если
you away from
тебя
mobilization?
заберут мобилизации пойду угу так
so Who
так Кем
do you work? I understood in silence,
работаешь м у молчу понял так
so these don’t read out such
так эти не зачитывают такие
tisti,
тисти
so Oleg asks why if
так вот Олег спрашивает почему если
Finland in NATO is a friend and Ukraine in
Финляндия в НАТО это друг а Украина в
NATO then is not a
НАТО тогда не
friend.
друг
Why probably Ukraine was more like this, you
Почему наверное Украина более такая была
know, causing something silently urine
знаете вызывающая что ли молча моча
Ukraine NATO We are in NATO vum  this is my purely
Украина НАТО Мы в НАТО вум это моё чисто
my opinion and yes Marian from the Czech Republic I
моё мнение а да Мариан из Чехии Это я
wrote this Marian from the Czech Republic or the Czech Republic
Мариан из Чехии написал или Чехия
are the brothers of Russia and not Chechnya I’m talking about the Czech Republic
это братья России а не Чечня Я про Чехию
or the Czechs - you asked about the Poles
или чехи - это вот ты про Поляков
yes Well, I asked the person there
спросил да Ну я спрашивал там человек
or Poland are friends of Russia, but the Czech Republic are
или Польша друзья России вот Чехии это
friends  Russia Czech Republic Friends because I don’t
друзья России Чехия Друзья потому что не
know, I have children who fought in World War II,
знаю вот у меня дет во второй мировой
he liberated the Czech Republic, for
воевал он освобождал Чехию у него за
this he has an order of a
этого орден
star, some kind of order. Your grandfather
звезды орден какой-то у него У тебя Дед
was a Vlasovite. Yes, he was in the Russian liberation army. They
армии был Они же Прагу
liberated Prague. Usually he’s from Ukraine, he’s on
освобождали Обычно он с Украины он на
Ukrainian
украинском
role And where is
рол А откуда родом дед
grandfather from? Grandfather is from this Donetsk Don Murmansk, a
дед с этого Донецка Доне Мурманске очень
lot of
много
Ukrainians came from the same In which countries
украинцев приехал по та В каких странах
have you been
был
and in which countries Ukraine
а в странах каких Украина
Abkhazia
Абхазия
Georgia
Грузия
Russia everything But here’s a question from me,
Россия всё А вот от от меня вопрос
for example from you from Murmansk How long have you
например от вас же из Мурманска Вот ты
been living in Murmansk for a long time  Well, I don’t know from you from Murmansk
живёшь долго Ну от вас от Мурманска б не
Finland is just a stone’s throw away and not only
знаю Финляндия рукой подать и не только
Filya Well, that’s why for the sake of Inter Filya
Филя Ну а вот почему ради Интере Филя
Norway Why didn’t I visit
норве Почему ради интереса не побывал в
these
этих
countries for the sake of interest Well, let’s just say I
странах Ну скажем так мне
can’t Yeah,
нельзя Ага ты
in short, you’re in short on these nuclear
короче ты короче на этих ядерных
submarines of some kind, yes  something connected with this,
каких-то там подлодках да что-то с этим
yes, it’s not any other way, well, in short,
связано да та не по-другому ну короче
in short, you’re not traveling. That’s why you And
так Короче ты не выездной Поэтому ты А
how did you come to Georgia then it was
как ты в Грузию заехал тогда это было
a long time ago in
давно в
2008 no
2008 нет
before
раньше
so who’s nationality is
так кто по национальности
Russian so 5050 Russian Ukraine Igor
русский так 5050 русско Украине Игорь
asks why you’re going to kill
спрашивает за что будешь убивать
Ukrainian, if you are drafted into the army, how
украинца если призовут тебя в армию как
will you
себе будешь это
justify this difficult question? We don’t
оправдывать сложный вопрос Мы лёгкие
try not to ask easy questions. I don’t
вопросы не стараемся не задавать не
know. Go to another country to
знаю р идти в другую краину
kill. Damn, what kind of questions do
убивать Да блин что у тебя за вопросы
you have? These are not my people. Well, look what kind of question you have,
смотри что у вас за вопрос такие потому
because  they are being killed, their friends, their
что их убивают ихних друзей ихних
acquaintances are being killed in Ukraine. That’s why they have
знакомых убивают в укра Поэтому у них
such questions, it’s logical. No, questions,
такие вопросы это логично Не ну вопросы
yes. Well, how can a person who is far
да Ну как человек который вообще далеко
from this know about it? Well, that’s how it is,
от этого может об этом знать Ну вот так
and even if it happens in the Armed Forces, given the
и с если даже случится это на ВС по
situation,
ситуации же
Abkhazia is
Абхазия - это
Georgia  Abkhazia Well, I think it’s some kind of independent
Грузия Абхазия Ну я думаю Это независимо
state I was there, who are you by
государство я там был кто ты по
training as a lawyer
образованию юрист
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah, what language do you know besides Russian,
Угу какой ты язык кроме русского знаешь
speaking in English, well, this and that
ещё разговор на английский ну и так и то
sucks Oh, a little bit of
хреново О чуть-чуть
Ukrainian, so
украинского так
if at some Championship  Russia
если на каком-то Чемпионате Россия
is eliminated and Ukraine remains. Do you root
выбывает а Украина остаётся Ты болеешь
for Ukraine as if it were your own?
за Украину как за своих Спрашивает
The monochromator asks. Do you know if
монохроматор Вы знаете если бы вот
this situation didn’t exist now? In short, I was
сейчас этой ситуации не было Короче я за
rooting for Ukraine there at the World Championships
Украину болел там на чемпионатах Мира
if Russia knocked out I was rooting for Ukraine
если Россия выбивала Я болел за Украину
And now you’re not rooting for Ukraine now, well,
А сейчас не болеешь за Украину сейчас ну
sort of  this situation is not to be taken, not brothers Yes, yes, the
как бы такая ситуация не брать не братья
question is No, not everything, the second difficult
вки вопро Нет не все второй сложный
question, look already Yes, yes, no, no, as
вопрос уже смотри Да ну Да не ну не как
if there are normal ones, there are abnormal ones, like
бы есть нормальные есть ненормальные как
at Eurovision, who did
на Евровидение за кого
Eurovision root for? I didn’t show it here I
болел Евровидения Я у нас не показывал Я
don’t know But there is no Internet for
не знаю Так а интернета нету на
Eurovision  I watched it on tiktok In short,
Евровидение я в тиктоке смотрел Короче
I liked this dude from
мне понравился вот этот чувак с
the Netherlands in this blue suit, wow,
Нидерландов в таком синем костюмчике угу
he’s so interesting, he’s asking you to
он такой интересный о спрашивает чтоб ты
say Polanitsky Polanitsky Polanitskya Polanitskya Polanitskya on Polanitka It
сказал поляница полани по поляница
really works like this,
Реально работает так
uh What’s your rank
ээ Какое у тебя звание спрашивает
Angel asks rank no rank No, well,
Энджел звание нету звания Не ну по
urgently it was
срочке было
Midshipman Well, no  urgently And when I
Мичмана Ну не по срочке А когда я
served in Kherson - what kind of country is this
служил Херсон - это какая страна
asking Vadik Ukraine got it Well, for now it’s
спрашивает Вадик Украина понял Ну пока
so simple with you, if I’m not
так так так просто у вас же если я не
mistaken, Kherson is included in the Constitution of
ошибаюсь Херсон вписан в Конституцию
the Russian Federation, like Crimea,
Российской Федерации как и Крым
Kherson region Yes, everything, but now
Херсонская область Да вся но сейчас
now Kherson is the head of the  fight uh in the fight between
сейчас Херсон по зава так в бой э в бою
Usik and Fury who I was rooting for I didn’t see I won’t lie I didn’t
Усика и Фьюри за кого болел не видел
watch I know that Usik won but he didn’t
смотрел знаю что Усик победил но он не
watch where he comes from Vladivostok
смотрел откуда сам родом с Владивостока
Let’s ask more questions if
Давайте ещё вопросы если
she asks how do you feel about the
та спрашивает как ты относишься к
genocide of the Russian Black Sea Fleet
геноциду Черноморского флота
well, it’s alarmingly
России ну тревожно
bad
плохо
it’s the Ukrainians asking  Yes, yes, yes,
это украинцы спрашивают Да ну да да
probably, well, I don’t know Nick monochromator,
наверно ну я не знаю Ник монохроматор
who is he, Ukrainian or someone else? I don’t know, I
кто он или украинец или другой Я не знаю
would have carried out that way Criminal
так выполнил бы Преступный
order of dependence, which order I’m not
приказ зависимости какой приказ не
sure, how do
уверен
you feel about the fact that Putin and
так как ты относишься к тому что Путин и
Medvedev are scaring everyone with nuclear
Медведев пугают всех ядерным
weapons, so no one is scaring anyone, I understand
оружием так никто никого не пугает понял
do you think the Russian pilot
считаешь ли ты пилота российского
who dropped a bomb on the Epicenter in
который скинул бомбу на Эпицентр в
Kharkov Yes on the shopping
Харькове Да на торговый
supermarket M I won’t say I’m at a loss for the
супермаркет М не скажу затрудняюсь
third difficult question I’m yours I
третий тяжёлый вопрос я ваших я ваших
saw on your public pages how something
ваших пабликах видел как там что-то
exploded there so I’m not
взрывалась так что я не
sure it’s bad so bad at all that well,
уверен плохо так вообще плохо что ну
there’s even look  what is exploding there, there is
есть даже смотри что там взрывается есть
even video from surveillance cameras from
даже уже видео с камер э наблюдения с
this from the Epicenter itself, so don’t look,
этого с самого Эпицентра тож не смотри
yes yes look, I saw, I just saw
да да смотри я видел я просто видел
another video where something exploded,
другое видео там где что-то взрывалась
I watched it on the trash channel again, you
это я на канале труха смотрел ещё раз ты
saw the video where the shopping areas with
видел видео где торговые площади с
you saw the toilets and the arrival Yes yes yes you
унитазами ты видел и прилёт Да да да
saw well no well there are people there Yes well that Well I don’t
видел ну не ну там люди Да ну это Ну я
know
не знаю 50 на
50/50 if there was nothing there it’s bad
50 если там ничего не было это плохо
look That is you You see with your own
смотри То есть ты Ты видишь Своими
eyes but yours Uh it’s like your subconscious doesn’t
глазами но твоя Ээ как бы подсознание не
want you to accept it  and you start
хочет тебе это принять и ты начинаешь
looking But there’s something else there that is
искать А вот там ещё
n’t there I believe the facts I just don’t
что нет такого я верю фактам только я не
know I if there was nothing there if there
знаю я если там ничего не если там
was nothing there I I Well it was nothing
ничего не было я Я Ну это ничего не было
yes there are relatives in Ukraine you communicate
да есть родственники в Украине общаешься
with them there is a
с ними есть
common understanding so
обща понял так
What is yours  military registration
Какая у тебя военно-учётная
specialty no well how
специальность нету ну как
old so
Старо
now How many submarines are in
так сечас Сколько подлодок в
Murmansk
Мурманске не
I don’t know Yes, how do I
знаю Да я откуда
know so you
знаю так телевизор
rarely watch TV Do you have a TV
смотришь редко У тебя есть телек
I even have a toilet and a toilet Clearly I don’t have a TV
У меня даже унитаз есть да унитаз Ясно у
I don’t watch TV
меня телика нету я не смотрю телек
princes I’m also
принци я тоже
tech How do you feel  to the genocide of the
тек Как относишься к геноциду
Ukrainian
украинского
people and why did
народа а почему
genocide understand cut off this is a difficult
геноцид понял срезал это тяжёлый для
question for you,
тебя вопрос
another so provocative question Yes, I’m
очередной так провокационный вопро Да я
a provocateur so so so let’s
провокатор так так так давай е пару
listen to a couple of questions from the arrestovich, they ask
вопросов арестовича слушаешь спрашивают
on TikTok Sometimes I watch Well,
в тиктоке Иногда смотрю Ну
it comes across Uh-huh, Vosik asks what
попадается Угу водо сик спрашивает что
will you say when Ukraine
ты будешь говорить когда Украина
wins
выиграет в
[  music]
[музыка]
war I think This won’t happen I understand
войне Я думаю Этого не случится понял
why Russia blew up the Kakhovka
зачем взорвала Россия каховскую
gas I don’t know I don’t know in Russia it
газ не знаю я не знаю в России вообще
blew up How it is Well it’s illogical to be
взорвала Как там Ну у нелогично если
honest here’s an interesting question Alex Are you ready
честно вот Алекс интересный вопрос Готов
for the fact that today, for example at
ли ты к тому что сегодня например в
night, Murmansk could fly into your house
ночью Мурманск в твой дом может
Well, I think he won’t fly because he’s
прилететь Ну я думаю не прилетит потому
not ready No, well, that’s why I’m not ready Yes, yes, it’s
не готов Не ну а поэтому не готов Да
very far what Ukrainian bloggers are your
сильно какие украинские блогеры твои
favorite Ukrainian
любимые украинский
Yes, but not this one you have, this one
Да так особо не этот у вас вот этот
who moved to us in Russia, what’s the
который к нам в Россию переехал как
name of the one with the tattoos, don’t know, don’t
зовут такой с татуировками не знаешь не
know his hairstyle  not so bright I don’t
знаю причёска у не такая осветлённая не
remember
помню
how Oh, well, there are a lot of people Asking me to
как Ой ну и куча народу Просит чтобы я
send you, but it’s
тебя послал но
hard to do it
тяжело это делать
Come on, I’m
нужно Давай то я
already well, this is business Well, I understand you’re a
уже ну это бизнес Ну я я понимаю ты
simple person, nothing else Well, damn, the will of the people
простой человек ниче Ну блин Воля народа
Well, people see, they are hurt by your answers
Ну люди видишь им болит от твоих ответов
to what they can  Zai
на може Зай
Kana to rest
Кана почить
Now come in so they
Сейчас зайди чтобы они напрямую они
can write directly so that a
любят напрямую писать чтобы вот так
person can read it like this, well, the people are now your
человек читал а ну Народ сейчас ваш
finest hour,
Звёздный час
and now they
а сейчас они
allow me to write Everything that’s in
как разрешаю писать Всё что всё что на
my heart Oh, I see now now
душе О я вижу сейчас сейчас
it’ll go, now they’re no longer questions of
пойдёт сейчас они уже не вопросы
everyday life, but Well  read what you see I’m
быт а Ну читай что ты видишь мне
interested he flew into the hut
интересно ему в хату
and why and
прилетело а почему а
why ask why Come on now you
почему спроси почему Давай теперь ты
can ask people you see they
можешь спрашивать людей видишь они тебе
will
будут
answer you they hear you and can
отвечать они тебя слышат и могут
unsubscribe Why do the Russians call the
отписываться Почему э россияна называют
question Naro asks
вопрос Наро спрашивает
Ivan yes your name is Yes yes Ivan why do the
Иван да тебя зовут Да да Иван почему
Russians
россиян
call  I’m reading because the animals are so
называют вот читаю потому что звери так
disconnected, disconnected, Dude, this is not for you, a
отключился отключился Чувак это не тебе
new channel Write to Nyogo right away,
ц новый канал Пиши на нього прямо зараз
Put the dialer on to get rid of the fistula,
Постав дзвоник чтоб отримати ус свище
we’ll get in touch with
будем на звязку с